Oliver Otis Howard Papers M091 M091
George J. Mitchell Department of Special Collections & Archives, Bowdoin College Library, Brunswick, Maine 04011
- M91.3: Correspondence, Freedmen's Bureau period, May 1865-Spring 1874, M91.3; 12.0 linear feet
  - 1867 Jul 01 - 1867 Jul 03 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - 1867 Jul 04 - 1867 Jul 07 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - 1867 Jul 08 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - 1867 Jul 09 - 1867 Jul 11 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - 1867 Jul 12 - 1867 Jul 15 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - 1867 Jul 16 - 1867 Jul 17 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - 1867 Jul 18 - 1867 Jul 19 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - 1867 Jul 20 - 1867 Jul 22 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - 1867 Jul 23 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - 1867 Jul 24 - 1867 Jul 26 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - 1867 Jul 27 - 1867 Jul 31 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - 1867 Aug 01 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - 1867 Aug 02 - Aug 03 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - 1867 Aug 04 - 1867 Aug 05 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 1867 Aug 06 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - 1867 Aug 07 - 1867 Aug 09 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 1867 Aug 10 - 1867 Aug 12 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - 1867 Aug 13 - 1867 Aug 14 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - 1867 Aug 15 - 1867 Aug 16 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - 1867 Aug 17 - 1867 Aug 19 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - 1867 Aug 20 - 1867 Aug 21 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - 1867 Aug 22 - 1867 Aug 23 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - 1867 Aug 24 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - 1867 Aug 25 - 1867 Aug 27 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - 1867 Aug 28 - 1867 Aug 31 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - 1867 Sep 01 - 1867 Sep 03 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - 1867 Sep 04 - 1867 Sep 05 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - 1867 Sep 06 - 1867 Sep 10 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - 1867 Sep 11 - 1867 Sep 13 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - 1867 Sep 14 - 1867 Sep 16 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - 1867 Sep 17 - 1867 Sep 18 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - 1867 Sep 19 - 1867 Sep 22 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - 1867 Sep 23 - 1867 Sep 24 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - 1867 Sep 25 - 1867 Sep 28 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - 1867 Sep 29 - 1867 Sep 30 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - 1867 Oct 01 - 1867 Oct 02 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - 1867 Oct 03 - 1867 Oct 05 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - 1867 Oct 06 - 1867 Oct 08 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - 1867 Oct 09 - 1867 Oct 11 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - 1867 Oct 12 - 1867 Oct 14 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - 1867 Oct 15 - 1867 Oct 16 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - 1867 Oct 17 - 1867 Oct 20 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - 1867 Oct 21 - 1867 Oct 22 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - 1867 Oct 23 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - 1867 Oct 24 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - 1867 Oct 25 - 1867 Oct 28 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - 1867 Oct 29 - 1867 Oct 31 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - 1867 Nov 01 - 1867 Nov 02 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - 1867 Nov 03 - 1867 Nov 06 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - 1867 Nov 07 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - 1867 Nov 08 - 1867 Nov 11 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - 1867 Nov 12 - 1867 Nov 17 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - 1867 Nov 18 - 1867 Nov 19 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - 1867 Nov 20 - 1867 Nov 24 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - 1867 Nov 25 - 1867 Nov 27 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - 1867 Nov 28 - 1867 Nov 30 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - 1867 Dec 01 - 1867 Dec 04 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - 1867 Dec 05 - 1867 Dec 09 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - 1867 Dec 10 - 1867 Dec 12 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - 1867 Dec 13 - 1867 Dec 16 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - 1867 Dec 17 - 1867 Dec 19 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - 1867 Dec 20 - 1867 Dec 22 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - 1867 Dec 23 - 1867 Dec 24 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - 1867 Dec 25 - 1867 Dec 29 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - 1867 Dec 30 - 1867 Dec 31 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - 1868 Jan 01 - 1868 Jan 04 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - 1868 Jan 06 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - 1868 Jan 05 - 1868 Jan 07 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - 1868 Jan 08 - 1868 Jan 10 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - 1868 Jan 11 - 1868 Jan 13 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - 1868 Jan 14 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - 1868 Jan 15 - 1868 Jan 17 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - 1868 Jan 18 - 1868 Jan 24 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - 1868 Jan 25 - 1868 Jan 27 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - 1868 Jan 28 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - 1868 Jan 29 - 1868 Jan 31 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - 1868 Feb 01 - 1868 Feb 02 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - 1868 Feb 03 - 1868 Feb 04 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - 1868 Feb 05 - 1868 Feb 06 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - 1868 Feb 07 - 1868 Feb 10 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - 1868 Feb 11 - 1868 Feb 13 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - 1868 Feb 14 - 1868 Feb 18 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - 1868 Feb 19 - 1868 Feb 21 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - 1868 Feb 22 - 1868 Feb 25 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - 1868 Feb 26 - 1868 Feb 29 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - 1868 Mar 01 - 1868 Mar 02 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - 1868 Mar 03 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - 1868 Mar 04 - 1868 Mar 07 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - 1868 Mar 08 - 1868 Mar 10 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - 1868 Mar 11 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - 1868 Mar 12 - 1868 Mar 17 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - 1868 Mar 18 - 1868 Mar 20 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - 1868 Mar 21 - 1868 Mar 26 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - 1868 Mar 27 - 1868 Mar 28 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - 1868 Mar 29 - 1868 Mar 31 (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - 1868 Apr 01 - 1868 Apr 03 (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - 1868 Apr 04 - 1868 Apr 08 (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - 1868 Apr 09 - 1868 Apr 10 (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - 1868 Apr 11 - 1868 Apr 13 (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - 1868 Apr 14 - 1868 Apr 15 (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - 1868 Apr 16 (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - 1868 Apr 17 - 1868 Apr 22 (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - 1868 Apr 18 (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - 1868 Apr 23 - 1868 Apr 26 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 1868 Apr 27 - 1868 Apr 30 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 1868 May 01 - 1868 May 07 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - 1868 May 08 - 1868 May 11 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - 1868 May 12 - 1868 May 16 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - 1868 May 17 - 1868 May 22 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - 1868 May 23 - 1868 May 25 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - 1868 May 26 - 1868 May 28 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - 1868 May 29 - 1868 May 31 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - 1868 Jun 01 - 1868 Jun 03 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - 1868 Jun 04 - 1868 Jun 08 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - 1868 Jun 09 - 1868 Jun 12 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - 1868 Jun 13 - 1868 Jun 14 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - 1868 Jun 15 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - 1868 Jun 16 - 1868 Jun 18 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - 1868 Jun 19 - 1868 Jun 26 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - 1868 Jun 27 - 1868 Jun 30 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - 1868 Jul 01 - 1868 Jul 10 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - 1868 Jul 11 - 1868 Jul 14 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - 1868 Jul 15 - 1868 Jul 20 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - 1868 Jul 21 - 1868 Jul 31 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - 1868 Aug 01 - 1868 Aug 03 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - 1868 Aug 04 - 1868 Aug 07 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - 1868 Aug 08 - 1868 Aug 13 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - 1868 Aug 14 - 1868 Aug 21 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - 1868 Aug 22 - 1868 Aug 31 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - 1868 Sep 01 - 1868 Sep 09 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - 1868 Sep 10 - 1868 Sep 18 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - 1868 Sep 19 - 1868 Sep 20 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - 1868 Sep 21 - 1868 Sep 23 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - 1868 Sep 24 - 1868 Sep 26 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - 1868 Sep 27 - 1868 Sep 29 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - 1868 Sep 30 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - 1868 Oct 01 - 1868 Oct 04 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - 1868 Oct 05 - 1868 Oct 07 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - 1868 Oct 08 - 1868 Oct 13 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - 1868 Oct 14 - 1868 Oct 17 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - 1868 Oct 18 - 1868 Oct 20 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - 1868 Oct 21 - 1868 Oct 26 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - 1868 Oct 27 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - 1868 Oct 28 - 1868 Oct 31 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - 1868 Nov 01 - 1868 Nov 03 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - 1868 Nov 04 - 1868 Nov 07 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - 1868 Nov 09 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - 1868 Nov 10 - 1868 Nov 12 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - 1868 Nov 13 - 1868 Nov 15 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - 1868 Nov 16 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - 1868 Nov 17 - 1868 Nov 19 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - 1868 Nov 20 - 1868 Nov 22 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - 1868 Nov 23 - 1868 Nov 24 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - 1868 Nov 25 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - 1868 Nov 26 - 1868 Nov 27 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - 1868 Nov 28 - 1868 Nov 30 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - 1868 Dec 01 - 1868 Dec 02 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - 1868 Dec 03 - 1868 Dec 04 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - 1868 Dec 05 - 1868 Dec 07 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - 1868 Dec 08 - 1868 Dec 10 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - 1868 Dec 11 - 1868 Dec 13 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - 1868 Dec 14 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - 1868 Dec 15 - 1868 Dec 17 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - 1868 Dec 18 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - 1868 Dec 19 - 1868 Dec 20 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - 1868 Dec 21 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - 1868 Dec 22 - 1868 Dec 23 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - 1868 Dec 24 - 1868 Dec 25 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - 1868 Dec 26 - 1868 Dec 28 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - 1868 Dec 29 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - 1868 Dec 30 - 1868 Dec 31 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - 1869 Jan 01 - 1869 Jan 04 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - 1869 Jan 05 - 1869 Jan 06 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - 1869 Jan 07 - 1869 Jan 08 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - 1869 Jan 09 - 1869 Jan 11 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - 1869 Jan 12 - 1869 Jan 14 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - 1869 Jan 15 - 1869 Jan 19 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - 1869 Jan 20 - 1869 Jan 24 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - 1869 Jan 25 - 1869 Jan 28 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - 1869 Jan 29 - 1869 Jan 31 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - 1869 Feb 01 - 1869 Feb 05 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - 1869 Feb 06 - 1869 Feb 08 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - 1869 Feb 09 - 1869 Feb 18 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - 1869 Feb 19 - 1869 Feb 21 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - 1869 Feb 22 - 1869 Feb 25 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - 1869 Feb 26 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - 1869 Feb 27 - 1869 Feb 28 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - 1869 Mar 01 - 1869 Mar 02 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - 1869 Mar 03 - 1869 Mar 04 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - 1869 Mar 05 - 1889 Mar 07 (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - 1869 Mar 08 - 1869 Mar 09 (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - 1869 Mar 10 - 1869 Mar 12 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - 1869 Mar 13 - 1869 Mar 15 (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - 1869 Mar 16 - 1869 Mar 17 (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - 1869 Mar 18 - 1869 Mar 19 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 1869 Mar 20 - 1869 Mar 22 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 1869 Mar 23 - 1869 Mar 26 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 1869 Mar 27 - 1869 Mar 31 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - 1869 Apr 01 - 1869 Apr 03 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - 1869 Apr 04 - 1869 Apr 05 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - 1869 Apr 06 - 1869 Apr 07 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - 1869 Apr 08 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - 1869 Apr 09 - 1869 Apr 10 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - 1869 Apr 11 - 1869 Apr 12 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - 1869 Apr 13 - 1869 Apr 14 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - 1869 Apr 15 - 1869 Apr 18 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - 1869 Apr 19 - 1869 Apr 20 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - 1869 Apr 21 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - 1869 Apr 22 - 1869 Apr 26 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - 1869 Apr 27 - 1869 Apr 30 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - 1869 May 01 - 1869 May 04 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - 1869 May 05 - 1869 May 06 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - 1869 May 07 - 1869 May 08 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - 1869 May 09 - 1869 May 11 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - 1869 May 12 - 1869 May 15 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - 1869 May 16 - 1869 May 19 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - 1869 May 20 - 1869 May 22 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - 1869 May 23 - 1869 May 24 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - 1869 May 25 - 1869 May 26 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - 1869 May 27 - 1869 May 29 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - 1869 May 30 - 1869 May 31 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - 1869 Jun 01 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - 1869 Jun 02 - 1869 Jun 06 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - 1869 Jun 07 - 1869 Jun 09 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - 1869 Jun 10 - 1869 Jun 14 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - 1869 Jun 15 - 1869 Jun 18 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - 1869 Jun 19 - 1869 Jun 21 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - 1869 Jun 22 - 1869 Jun 24 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - 1869 Jun 25 - 1869 Jun 27 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - 1869 Jun 28 - 1869 Jun 30 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - 1869 Jul 01 - 1869 Jul 05 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - 1869 Jul 06 - 1869 Jul 08 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - 1869 Jul 09 - 1869 Jul 13 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - 1869 Jul 14 - 1869 Jul 19 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - 1869 Jul 20 - 1869 Jul 22 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - 1869 Jul 23 - 1869 Jul 26 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - 1869 Jul 27 - 1869 Jul 28 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - 1869 Jul 29 - 1869 Jul 31 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - 1869 Aug 01 - 1869 Aug 04 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - 1869 Aug 05 - 1869 Aug 06 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - 1869 Aug 07 - 1869 Aug 09 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - 1869 Aug 10 - 1869 Aug 12 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - 1869 Aug 13 - 1869 Aug 14 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - 1869 Aug 15 - 1869 Aug 17 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - 1869 Aug 18 - 1869 Aug 24 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - 1869 Aug 25 - 1869 Aug 29 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - 1869 Aug 30 - 1869 Aug 31 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - 1869 Sep 01 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - 1869 Sep 02 - 1869 Sep 06 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - 1869 Sep 07 - 1869 Sep 10 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - 1869 Sep 11 - 1869 Sep 13 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - 1869 Sep 14 - 1869 Sep 18 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - 1869 Sep 19 - 1869 Sep 21 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - 1869 Sep 22 - 1869 Sep 25 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - 1869 Sep 26 - 1869 Sep 30 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - 1869 Oct 01 - 1869 Oct 02 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - 1869 Oct 03 - 1869 Oct 06 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - 1869 Oct 07 - 1869 Oct 09 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - 1869 Oct 10 - 1869 Oct 16 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - 1869 Oct 17 - 1869 Oct 21 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - 1869 Oct 22 - 1869 Oct 27 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - 1869 Oct 28 - 1869 Oct 31 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - 1869 Nov 01 - 1869 Nov 03 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - 1869 Nov 04 - 1869 Nov 07 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - 1869 Nov 08 - 1869 Nov 10 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - 1869 Nov 11 - 1869 Nov 12 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - 1869 Nov 13 - 1869 Nov 16 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - 1869 Nov 17 - 1869 Nov 18 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - 1869 Nov 19 - 1869 Nov 23 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - 1869 Nov 24 - 1869 Nov 25 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - 1869 Nov 26 - 1869 Nov 30 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - 1869 Dec 01 - 1869 Dec 06 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - 1869 Dec 07 - 1869 Dec 10 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - 1869 Dec 11 - 1869 Dec 13 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - 1869 Dec 14 - 1869 Dec 17 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - 1869 Dec 18 - 1869 Dec 22 (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - 1869 Dec 23 - 1869 Dec 28 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - 1869 Dec 29 - 1869 Dec 31 (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - 1870 Jan 01 - 1870 Jan 04 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 1870 Jan 05 - 1870 Jan 11 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 1870 Jan 12 - 1870 Jan 14 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - 1870 Jan 15 - 1870 Jan 18 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - 1870 Jan 19 - 1870 Jan 21 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - 1870 Jan 22 - 1870 Jan 24 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - 1870 Jan 25 - 1870 Jan 28 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - 1870 Jan 29 - 1870 Jan 31 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - 1870 Feb 01 - 1870 Feb 03 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - 1870 Feb 04 - 1870 Feb 07 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - 1870 Feb 08 - 1870 Feb 10 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - 1870 Feb 11 - 1870 Feb 14 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - 1870 Feb 15 - 1870 Feb 18 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - 1870 Feb 19 - 1870 Feb 23 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - 1870 Feb 24 - 1870 Feb 28 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - 1870 Mar 01 - 1870 Mar 04 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - 1870 Mar 05 - 1870 Mar 08 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - 1870 Mar 09 - 1870 Mar 10 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - 1870 Mar 11 - 1870 Mar 14 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - 1870 Mar 15 - 1870 Mar 16 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - 1870 Mar 17 - 1870 Mar 20 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - 1870 Mar 21 - 1870 Mar 23 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - 1870 Mar 24 - 1870 Mar 28 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - 1870 Mar 29 - 1870 Mar 31 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - 1870 Apr 01 - 1870 Apr 03 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - 1870 Apr 04 - 1870 Apr 07 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - 1870 Apr 08 - 1870 Apr 10 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - 1870 Apr 11 - 1870 Apr 13 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - 1870 Apr 14 - 1870 Apr 17 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - 1870 Apr 18 - 1870 Apr 21 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - 1870 Apr 22 - 1870 Apr 26 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - 1870 Apr 27 - 1870 Apr 30 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - 1870 May 01 - 1870 May 06 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - 1870 May 07 - 1870 May 10 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - 1870 May 11 - 1870 May 16 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - 1870 May 17 - 1870 May 25 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - 1870 May 26 - 1870 May 31 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - 1870 Jun 01 - 1870 Jun 06 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - 1870 Jun 07 - 1870 Jun 10 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - 1870 Jun 11 - 1870 Jun 14 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - 1870 Jun 15 - 1870 Jun 21 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - 1870 Jun 22 - 1870 Jun 27 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - 1870 Jun 28 - 1870 Jun 30 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - 1870 Jul 01 - 1870 Jul 09 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - 1870 Jul 10 - 1870 Jul 13 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - 1870 Jul 14 - 1870 Jul 15 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - 1870 Jul 16 - 1870 Jul 18 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - 1870 Jul 19 - 1870 Jul 21 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - 1870 Jul 22 - 1870 Jul 26 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - 1870 Jul 27 - 1870 Jul 31 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - 1870 Aug 01 - 1870 Aug 04 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - 1870 Aug 05 - 1870 Aug 08 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - 1870 Aug 09 - 1870 Aug 11 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - 1870 Aug 12 - 1870 Aug 15 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - 1870 Aug 16 - 1870 Aug 19 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - 1870 Aug 20 - 1870 Aug 25 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - 1870 Aug 26 - 1870 Aug 31 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - 1870 Sep 01 - 1870 Sep 03 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - 1870 Sep 04 - 1870 Sep 08 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - 1870 Sep 09 - 1870 Sep 15 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - 1870 Sep 16 - 1870 Sep 21 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - 1870 Sep 22 - 1870 Sep 27 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - 1870 Sep 28 - 1870 Sep 30 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - 1870 Oct 01 - 1870 Oct 03 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - 1870 Oct 04 - 1870 Oct 09 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - 1870 Oct 10 - 1870 Oct 12 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - 1870 Oct 13 - 1870 Oct 14 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - 1870 Oct 15 - 1870 Oct 17 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - 1870 Oct 18 - 1870 Oct 21 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - 1870 Oct 22 - 1870 Oct 25 (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - 1870 Oct 26 - 1870 Oct 31 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - 1870 Nov 01 - 1870 Nov 03 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - 1870 Nov 04 - 1870 Nov 09 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - 1870 Nov 10 - 1870 Nov 18 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - 1870 Nov 19 - 1870 Nov 22 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - 1870 Nov 23 - 1870 Nov 25 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - 1870 Nov 26 - 1870 Nov 28 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - 1870 Nov 29 - 1870 Nov 30 (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - 1870 Dec 01 - 1870 Dec 05 (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - 1870 Dec 06 - 1870 Dec 09 (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - 1870 Dec 10 - 1870 Dec 12 (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - 1870 Dec 13 - 1870 Dec 15 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 1870 Dec 16 - 1870 Dec 19 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - 1870 Dec 20 - 1870 Dec 25 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - 1870 Dec 26 - 1870 Dec 31 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - 1871 Jan 01 - 1871 Jan 06 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - 1871 Jan 07 - 1871 Jan 09 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - 1871 Jan 10 - 1871 Jan 12 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - 1871 Jan 13 - 1871 Jan 15 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - 1871 Jan 16 - 1871 Jan 18 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - 1871 Jan 19 - 1871 Jan 24 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - 1871 Jan 25 - 1871 Jan 27 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - 1871 Jan 28 - 1871 Jan 31 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - 1871 Feb 01 - 1871 Feb 03 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - 1871 Feb 04 - 1871 Feb 06 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - 1871 Feb 07 - 1871 Feb 10 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - 1871 Feb 11 - 1871 Feb 12 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - 1871 Feb 13 - 1871 Feb 14 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - 1871 Feb 15 - 1871 Feb 17 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - 1871 Feb 18 - 1871 Feb 20 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - 1871 Feb 21 - 1871 Feb 22 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - 1871 Feb 23 - 1871 Feb 25 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - 1871 Feb 26 - 1871 Feb 28 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - 1871 Mar 01 - 1871 Mar 03 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - 1871 Mar 04 - 1871 Mar 09 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - 1871 Mar 10 - 1871 Mar 13 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - 1871 Mar 14 - 1871 Mar 18 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - 1871 Mar 20 - 1871 Mar 31 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - 1871 Apr 01 - 1871 Apr 06 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - 1871 Apr 07 - 1871 Apr 08 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - 1871 Apr 09 - 1871 Apr 13 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - 1871 Apr 14 - 1871 Apr 16 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - 1871 Apr 17 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - 1871 Apr 18 - 1871 Apr 20 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - 1871 Apr 21 - 1871 Apr 24 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - 1871 Apr 24 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - 1871 Apr 25 - 1871 Apr 30 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - 1871 May 01 - 1871 May 04 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - 1871 May 05 - 1871 May 06 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - 1871 May 07 - 1871 May 09 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - 1871 May 10 - 1871 May 14 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - 1871 May 15 - 1871 May 18 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - 1871 May 19 - 1871 May 23 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - 1871 May 24 - 1871 May 31 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - 1871 Jun 01 - 1871 Jun 06 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - 1871 Jun 07 - 1871 Jun 14 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - 1871 Jun 15 - 1871 Jun 19 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - 1871 Jun 20 - 1871 Jun 25 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - 1871 Jun 26 - 1871 Jun 30 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - 1871 Jul 01 - 1871 Jul 06 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - 1871 Jul 07 - 1871 Jul 11 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - 1871 Jul 12 - 1871 Jul 17 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - 1871 Jul 18 - 1871 Jul 31 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - 1871 Aug 01 - 1871 Aug 07 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - 1871 Aug 08 - 1871 Aug 12 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - 1871 Aug 13 - 1871 Aug 16 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - 1871 Aug 17 - 1871 Aug 21 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - 1871 Aug 22 - 1871 Aug 31 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - 1871 Sep 01 - 1871 Sep 03 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - 1871 Sep 04 - 1871 Sep 06 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - 1871 Sep 07 - 1871 Sep 10 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - 1871 Sep 11 - 1871 Sep 13 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - 1871 Sep 14 - 1871 Sep 15 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - 1871 Sep 16 - 1871 Sep 19 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - 1871 Sep 20 - 1871 Sep 26 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - 1871 Sep 27 - 1871 Sep 30 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - 1871 Oct 01 - 1871 Oct 07 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - 1871 Oct 08 - 1871 Oct 12 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - 1871 Oct 13 - 1871 Oct 18 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - 1871 Oct 19 - 1871 Oct 23 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - 1871 Oct 24 - 1871 Oct 26 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - 1871 Oct 27 - 1871 Oct 31 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - 1871 Nov 01 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - 1871 Nov 02 - 1871 Nov 05 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - 1871 Nov 06 - 1871 Nov 10 (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - 1871 Nov 11 - 1871 Nov 17 (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - 1871 Nov 18 - 1871 Nov 24 (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - 1871 Nov 25 - 1871 Nov 30 (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - 1871 Dec 01 - 1871 Dec 07 (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - 1871 Dec 08 - 1871 Dec 12 (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - 1871 Dec 13 - 1871 Dec 20 (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - 1871 Dec 21 - 1871 Dec 25 (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - 1871 Dec 26 - 1871 Dec 31 (Box 10, Folder 82)
  - 1872 Jan 01 - 1872 Jan 31 (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - 1872 Feb 01 - 1872 Feb 05 (Box 10, Folder 84)
  - 1872 Feb 06 - 1872 Feb 09 (Box 10, Folder 85)
  - 1872 Feb 10 - 1872 Feb 14 (Box 10, Folder 86)
  - 1872 Feb 15 - 1872 Feb 19 (Box 10, Folder 87)
  - 1872 Feb 20 - 1872 Feb 22 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - 1872 Feb 23 - 1872 Feb 25 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 1872 Feb 26 - 1872 Feb 29 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - 1872 Mar 01 - 1872 Mar 03 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - 1872 Mar 04 - 1872 Mar 05 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - 1872 Mar 06 - 1872 Mar 09 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - 1872 Mar 10 - 1872 Mar 31 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - 1872 Apr 01 - 1872 Apr 12 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - 1872 Apr 13 - 1872 Apr 30 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - 1872 May 01 - 1872 May 15 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - 1872 May 16 - 1872 May 31 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - 1872 Jun 01 - 1872 Jun 16 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - 1872 Jun 17 - 1872 Jun 30 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - 1872 Jun 29 - 1872 Aug 12 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - 1872 Jul 01 - 1872 Jul 09 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - 1872 Jul 10 - 1872 Jul 30 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - 1872 Aug 01 - 1872 Aug 22 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - 1872 Aug 23 - 1872 Aug 31 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - 1872 Sep 01 - 1872 Sep 30 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - 1872 Oct 01 - 1872 Oct 12 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - 1872 Oct 13 - 1872 Oct 31 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - 1872 Nov 01 - 1872 Nov 12 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - 1872 Nov 13 - 1872 Nov 19 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - 1872 Nov 20 - 1872 Nov 24 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - 1872 Nov 25 - 1872 Nov 30 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - 1872 Dec 01 - 1872 Dec 06 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - 1872 Dec 07 - 1872 Dec 14 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - 1872 Dec 15 - 1872 Dec 19 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - 1872 Dec 20 - 1872 Dec 25 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - 1872 Dec 26 - 1872 Dec 31 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - 1873 Jan 01 - 1873 Jan 07 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - 1873 Jan 08 - 1873 Jan 15 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - 1873 Jan 16 - 1873 Jan 19 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - 1873 Jan 20 - 1873 Jan 24 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - 1873 Jan 25 - 1873 Jan 31 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - 1873 Feb 01 - 1873 Feb 04 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - 1873 Feb 05 - 1873 Feb 10 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - 1873 Feb 11 - 1873 Feb 18 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - 1873 Feb 19 - 1873 Feb 25 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - 1873 Feb 26 - 1873 Feb 28 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - 1873 Mar 01 - 1873 Mar 06 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - 1873 Mar 07 - 1873 Mar 10 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - 1873 Mar 11 - 1873 Mar 13 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - 1873 Mar 14 - 1873 Mar 16 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - 1873 Mar 17 - 1873 Mar 22 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - 1873 Mar 23 - 1873 Mar 27 (Box 11, Folder 46)